For every type of audio charge, I need a drawer and I need a calculation in the drawer.
Because I need to know how much extra money I need for a month if my one EMI is missed.
So I need to know how much extra money I need.
Because some banks have a 24-step bank.
I need to know how much extra money I need.
Even before taking a loan, I need to tell the bank to not take this bank.
If it has a 0.1% interest rate, then take that bank.
But don't take this bank, because if even one EMI is missed, you have to withdraw double money.
This is also a part of the intelligence.
I need to know how much extra money I need for a month if my one EMI is missed.
I need a drawer like that.
And I need to know the underlines. I need to click them and do the calculations.
We need to put labels on the bank.
For example, Jammu and Kashmir Bank.
It is one of the least penalty for EMI misses bank.
And Indus land bank is one of the highest penalties for EMI misses bank.
We need to tell this to the intelligence.
Interest rate is extraordinary.
We also need an overdue charge and EMI bounce charge.
We need to fit that into the calculations.
If we click on the overdue charge, we need to do the calculations.
If one EMI is missed for a month, we need total extra money.
Including EMI bounce charge.
We also need this intelligence, which is already visible here.